

# **Web Developer**

671 S. Pine Drive Bailey, CO 80421 864-449-7072 frazierr2@gmail.com ThinkFrazier.com github/frazierr2

## **Objective**

As a graduate of an accelerated front end web development program, I am seeking a position that will allow me to use and grow my new skills as a developer, utilize my past experience as a system administrator and a tech support analyst to be a well-versed and unique asset to any team.

### RELEVANT SKILLS

### **LANGUAGE AND PRACTICES**

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

JSX

Git and GitHub

**JSON** 

AJAX

RESTful Api's

# FRAMEWORKS AND LIBRARIES

Backbone JS

React JS

Underscore JS

**Bootstrap** 

Sass

Handlebars

jQuery

## **PROJECT**

#### **U-GRUB**

https://frazierr2.github.io/final-project/

The goal for U-Grub is to allow you, the user, to record your restaurant experience and later recall the things you liked, didn't like, food you ate and more. If you're traveling, no worries, we have you covered there also. Simply go to the Search Local Eateries tab and type in your location and you will be given a list of local restaurants with all the information you will need to make an informed decision.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Front-End Engineering**

The Iron Yard, September 2016 - December 2016

# **Bachelors of Science in Business Administration and Sociology**

Winthrop University, August 2004 - May 2009

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### SYSTEM INTEGRATION SPECIALIST

**Lucas Systems Inc.** 

May 2014 - August 2016

Liaison between Help Desk and the Development team working with code debugging of frequent issues and passing up to Development when bigger issues arise.

Install Point-of-Sale systems in restaurants.

Trained corporate staff and restaurant managers on our software platform.

Provide technical assistance and support in person, phone and electronically related to computer systems, hardware and software.

# IT COORDINATOR, WEBMASTER, YOUTH MINISTER

# Mount Tabor United Methodist Church May 2009 - May 2014

Designed and managed two websites through two campuses using WordPress, HTML5 and CSS3.

Troubleshoot, diagnose and repair equipment and networks across multiple campuses.

Managed Social Media aspects of the church and ministries. Recruit, equip and supervise a group of dedicated adult volunteers to lead the Middle School youth ministry of the churches two campuses.